{
  "response_code":0,
  "results":[
    {
      "category":"Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"In the &quot;Shrek&quot; film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"Geography",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"General Knowledge",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"Entertainment: Board Games",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The Angry Video Game Nerd&#039;s alter ego is &quot;Board James&quot;.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"Animals",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"A caterpillar has more muscles than humans do.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"Politics",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"Science & Nature",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"General Knowledge",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"Entertainment: Books",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"The Harry Potter series of books, combined, are over 1,000,000 words in length.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
}